<resources>
    <string name="app_name">homework_13.6</string>
    <string name="title1">Mystery over Taj Mahal rooms</string>
    <string name="news1"> Regarded as one of the Seven Wonders of the World, Taj Mahal, is known for the story of love it depicts. Taj Mahal is an \"awe-inspiring\" monument which is a \"timeless testament\" to the rich and diverse beauty of the Indian culture.</string>
    <string name="news2"> India\'s cricketing establishment has over the years shown patience in grooming a pack of world-class bowlers but in near future, the genuine pace of Umran Malik will be hard to ignore, feels Ian Chappell. Chappell says that the advent of IPL has acted as a catalyst for India\'s \"enormous depth in pace bowling\" and it is not showing any signs of abating.</string>

    <string name="title2">Genuine pace of Umran hard to ignore</string>
    <string name="title3">Want to finish this IPL on a roll: Sams</string>
<string name="news3">Mumbai Indians pacer Daniel Sams, who contributed to the team\'s two successive wins in IPL-15, says the five-time champions want to finish the season on a "bit of a roll", having failed to make the playoffs. Sams, who has picked up seven wickets from as many matches, feels his team-mates are motivated to win their remaining matches.</string>
    <string name="title4">Disha Patani Joins The Project K Family!</string>
<string name="news4">Nag Ashwin"s sci-fi Project K, is one of the most ambitious not to mention one of India"s most expensive films of all time, speaking volumes for the scale the entertainer has been mounted on. Joining the Project K family now is Disha Patani, who has been roped in for an interesting role in the film. The young star was welcomed to the team with a special gift</string>
    <string name="title5">Mother\'s Day 2022: Aamir Khan With His Ammi Zeenat Hussein</string>
<string name="news5">Be it on-screen or in real life, Aamir Khan is a man who knows how to respect and exhibit values and emotions. He is truly a family man and is frequently seen sharing his love for them with the audience. Today, On the occasion of Mother\'s Day, Aamir was seen celebrating the day with his Ammi Zeenat Hussein, his sister, Nikhat Khan, and brother-in-law, Santosh Hegde</string>
    <string name="title6">Hasaranga fifer powers RCB to big win</string>

    <string name="news6">Royal Challengers Bangalore strengthened their chances of sealing a playoff spot with a crushing 67-run win over Sunrisers Hyderabad in the ongoing edition of the Indian Premier League. The Challengers impressed with both bat and ball as they notched their seventh win of the season, and the second win on the trot.</string>
</resources>